

INGRID RABAY

User Interface Designer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

UI Designer with background in customer and administrative support and teaching.

Extensive experience in identifying and solving problems, giving and applying feedback, building rapport and communicating effectively. Professional key skills include Competitor Analysis, User Research, User Personas, User Flows, as well as Style Guides, Branding, Responsive Design, Wireframing, Prototyping, User testing and experience with tools such as Sketch, Adobe XD, Balsamiq and Flinto.

PROJECTS

SEECURITY - CAREERFOUNDRY - URL: https://www.behance.net/gallery/128161901/Security Role: UI/UX Designer | Tools: Sketch, Keynote

Seecurity is a money saving tool that allows users to record all income and expenses, gives
an overview of their overall financial health and personalized advice on which measures
they can take in order to achieve their financial goal. I did both the UX and UI portion of
this project, from user research to flows, to brand guidelines to wireframes, mock ups and
responsive design.

MEETR - CAREERFOUNDRY - URL: https://www.behance.net/gallery/129005845/Meetr Role: UI/UX Designer | Tools: Balsamiq, Sketch

Meetr is a shared calendar native app both for iOS and Android, that allows users to view
multiple contacts' calendars and availability at once as well as individually and share their
own. I started this project by conducting a competitive analysis, user research, created
personas, user flows, a proposal, wireframes, implemented sounds, haptics and gestures,
prototypes, conducted user testing with both iOS and Android users, and implemented
iterations based on user testing feedback.

THE HUB - CAREERFOUNDRY - URL: https://www.behance.net/gallery/129008093/The-Hub Role: UI/UX Designer | Tools: Sketch

• The Hub is a location-based recommendation app that helps users find places and activities they enjoy in their area. I was the UX and UI designer for this project where I conducted user research and interviews, created user personas, an MVP, userflows, wireframes, mood board and style guide, mockups and created responsive screens for tablet and desktop.

MUSICAL - CAREERFOUNDRY - URL: https://www.behance.net/gallery/129008305/Musical Role: UI/UX Designer | Tools: Sketch

Musical is a music app that allows users to create a profile, create personalized playlists, search for new artists and connect with their favorite apps on social media. I started this project by identifying the problem, performing a competitive analysis, doing user research and creating personas and analyzing user pain points and needs. Then I proceeded to provide a solution that met users needs, created user stories and user flows, a style guide, low and mid-fidelity wireframes, iterations, high-fidelity wireframes and mockups.

CONTACT

(617) 858 9107

www.behance.net/ingridrabay

Marlborough, MA

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- · UI elements, patterns and hierarchy
- · Design principles and heuristics
- · Wireframing and prototyping
- · Mobile app design
- · Using design systems
- · Designing responsive grids
- · Interaction design and animation
- · UX fundamentals and user psychology
- · User research and user testing
- Oser research and user testing
 Interpreting business requirements
- · Creating style guides
- · Building a cohesive brand
- · Designing symbols and iconography

EDUCATION

USER INTERFACE DESIGN

CareerFoundry - 2021

CELTA CERTIFICATION

University of Cambridge, UK - 2017

TOOLS

Sketch
Adobe XD
Figma
Balsamiq
Flinto
Keynote
MS Word

MSExcel

LANGUAGES

English Portuguese



CONTACT

irabay.uid@gmail.com

(617) 858 9107

www.behance.net/ingridrabay

Marlborough, MA

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

- · UI elements, patterns and hierarchy
- · Design principles and heuristics
- · Wireframing and prototyping
- · Mobile app design
- · Using design systems
- · Designing responsive grids
- · Interaction design and animation
- \cdot UX fundamentals and user psychology
- \cdot User research and user testing
- Interpreting business requirements
- · Creating style guides
- · Building a cohesive brand
- · Designing symbols and iconography

EDUCATION

USER INTERFACE DESIGN

CareerFoundry - 2021

CELTA CERTIFICATION

University of Cambridge, UK - 2017

TOOLS

Sketch Adobe XD Figma Balsamiq Flinto Keynote

MS Word

MSExcel

LANGUAGES

English Portuguese

INGRID RABAY

User Interface Designer

EXPERIENCE

REGISTRATIONS CLERK AND OFFICE ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Herb Connolly Chevrolet and Hyundai, Framingham, MA - Oct 2017 to May 2020

- Responsible for all vehicle registrations at fast paced and busy auto sales center. Through top-notch customer care and detailed processes, ensured all consumers had their vehicles registrations turned around quickly and on time.
- Advanced knowledge regularly to keep updated regarding DMV policies, vehicle stock and models, all financial procedures, communication protocol, and company operations. This improved the registration process, ensured vehicle information was always up to date, kept the funding process and daily operations straightforward.
- Owned end to end documentation processes with sales and finance team to ensure all documentation was completed and accurate. Resulted in high-customer satisfaction scores and reduced registrations turn-around time for customers.

ESL INSTRUCTOR

Brazilian American Center (BRACE) - Framingham, MA - September 2017 to December 2017

- Led multilingual English as a Second Language classes, teaching 12-18 students per class resulting in students' improved vocabulary, grammar, speaking, listening, reading and writing skills.
- Developed customized lesson plans based on learning students' needs and ability levels. Resulted in demonstrated individual students' success in language comprehension and acquisition.
- Ensured student and program success by offering assisted preparation for quizzes, and assessing their progress in stages. Students demonstrated measurable proof of increased language skills and fluency in class.

OFFICE ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT

Sharon Chen DMD Family Practice - Framingham, MA - December 2015 to May 2017

- Navigated between scheduling patients' appointments, while maintaining and filling production appointments to replace last minute cancellations. Resulted in increased patient satisfaction due to flexibility and a well-balanced schedule for the practice.
- Received calls in a friendly, professional manner, maneuvered a busy multi-line
 phone system and addressed patients' questions promptly which ensured patientstaff rapport and increased productivity.